

# 0

The Mandara Subdivision Tartaria Silang, Cavite



09063872934



glenntorres.video.editor @gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.co m/in/glenn-torres/

## **Glenn Torres**

### Video Editor

#### **Experience**

January 2021–Present
Video Editor • Project-Based

Video Editor • Project-Based August 2021- September 2021 YouTube Ads – Trademark Factory

Video Editor • Part-time
July 14, 2021 – September 2021
YouTube Video Editor
Observerpod – Jessica Moreno

May 2019 – Present
Frontend Web Developer | Video Editor ● Part-time

October 2015 – August 2017
IT Business Helpdesk Specialist

Technical Support

IBM

#### **Summary:**

I specialize in talking-head video shots with B-roll for smooth transitions and storytelling. I primarily use Premiere Pro for video editing (color grading, color correction, trimming, video assembly)Adobe Audition (audio processing, Noise reduction, etc.) And After Effects (visual effects, etc.)

#### **Education**

#### LCST, Urdaneta, Pangasinan

 Computer Technology 2000 - 2002

#### **Skills**

- Background noise removal
- Audio mixing
- Color grading, Sound effects, Text transition, Video animation, Visual



effects, cutting, trimming, video assembly, captioning.

### **Tools**

Adobe Premiere, After Effects, Adobe Audition, Slack, Frame.io

